(Penny:)-Who's Adam West?
-Who's Adam West?
(Sheldon:)What do the two of you
talk about after the coitus?
(Howard:)My guess is,
"Hey, four minutes. New record."
[HOWARD CHUCKLES]
(Howard:)That's why I'm the funny one.
(Leonard:)Anyway, we followed the guy
to this garage sale.
(Leonard:)They had the coolest stuff.
(Howard:)They were closing up.
We got this whole box for 60 bucks.
We didn't go through it.
There could be anything.
(Penny:)There a new girlfriend in there?
You might need one.
(Leonard:)No, but there is an original final draft
Ghostbusters script...
(Leonard:)...with actual slime stains.
[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
Oh, you're right, it's Ghostbusters ll.
Never mind.
(Howard:)Oh, my God.
(Howard:)An ALF doll.
(Howard:)When I was 11, my mother got me one
to help me sleep after my dad left.
(Howard:)I used to pretend that my dad
had moved to the planet Melmac...
...and ALF was gonna bring him back
to me.
(Howard:)But he never did.
[IN STRAINED VOICE]
Where's my daddy, puppet?
(Howard:)Where is he?
(Penny:)That is so sad.
(Sheldon:)No, what's sad is that you don't know
that Adam West was TV's Batman.